{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Electrostatic Painters","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40368/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40368,"taskName":"Metal Object or Surfaces - Paint Electrostatically","taskDescription":"Electrostatically Paint a Metal Object","xmTaskDescriptor":"Electrostatic Painters","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":1701,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Metal powdercoating coating coat statically","textMessagingName":"Paint Electstc","rolloverLongDesc":"Not done by most painters. A wire is attached to the metal object giving it an electrical charge that attracts \u0026 helps bind the paint that is then sprayed onto the object. Creates a long lasting finish. Used on anything metal including shutters, lawn furniture, appliances, file cabinets, etc.","rolloverShortDesc":"Uses an electrical charge to bind the paint.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Electrostatically Paint a Metal Object.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Electrostatic Painting \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":27,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Powdercoating Metal Object","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Metal Object or Surfaces - Paint Electrostatically","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Electrostatic Painting Project","urlName":"Metal-Object-or-Surfaces-Paint-Electrostatically","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Electrostatic Painting Contractors - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Metal,powdercoating,coat,statically,electro,powder,Electrostatically, electrostatic,","emcCategoryOid":-12059,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":662,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40368/":{"taskOID":40368,"originalTaskOID":40368,"setID":662,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4188,"questionDisplayText":"Select items for powder coating","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What items do you want powder coated? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4609,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Patio furniture","answerDisplayText":"Patio furniture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":816,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Appliance panels/parts","answerDisplayText":"Appliance panels/parts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3831,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Metal/Office furniture","answerDisplayText":"Metal/Office furniture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2431,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Filing cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Filing cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3810,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Metal doors and/or frames","answerDisplayText":"Metal doors and/or frames","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2898,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Gym/Playground equipment","answerDisplayText":"Gym/Playground equipment","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6221,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Swimming pool accessories","answerDisplayText":"Swimming pool accessories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5073,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Recreational equipment","answerDisplayText":"Recreational equipment","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1164,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Building parts (beams, supports, etc.)","answerDisplayText":"Building parts (beams, supports, etc.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5814,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Small miscellaneous parts","answerDisplayText":"Small miscellaneous parts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4188,"questionDisplayText":"Select items for powder coating","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What items do you want powder coated? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4609,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Patio furniture","answerDisplayText":"Patio furniture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":816,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Appliance panels/parts","answerDisplayText":"Appliance panels/parts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3831,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Metal/Office furniture","answerDisplayText":"Metal/Office furniture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2431,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Filing cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Filing cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3810,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Metal doors and/or frames","answerDisplayText":"Metal doors and/or frames","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2898,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Gym/Playground equipment","answerDisplayText":"Gym/Playground equipment","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6221,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Swimming pool accessories","answerDisplayText":"Swimming pool accessories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5073,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Recreational equipment","answerDisplayText":"Recreational equipment","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1164,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Building parts (beams, supports, etc.)","answerDisplayText":"Building parts (beams, supports, etc.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5814,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Small miscellaneous parts","answerDisplayText":"Small miscellaneous parts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4609,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Patio furniture","answerDisplayText":"Patio furniture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":816,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Appliance panels/parts","answerDisplayText":"Appliance panels/parts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3831,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Metal/Office furniture","answerDisplayText":"Metal/Office furniture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2431,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Filing cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Filing cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3810,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Metal doors and/or frames","answerDisplayText":"Metal doors and/or frames","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2898,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Gym/Playground equipment","answerDisplayText":"Gym/Playground equipment","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6221,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Swimming pool accessories","answerDisplayText":"Swimming pool accessories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5073,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Recreational equipment","answerDisplayText":"Recreational equipment","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1164,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Building parts (beams, supports, etc.)","answerDisplayText":"Building parts (beams, supports, etc.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5814,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Small miscellaneous parts","answerDisplayText":"Small miscellaneous parts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}